<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<blogs>
<blog><title>Boac Museum</title><author>Raj Kumar Paul</author><date>2023-05-27</date><content>
The building and lot was turned over to the National Museum of the Philippines (NMP) in 1992 by the Municipality 
of Boac. The building was restored, and the museum was eventually opened to the public on February 22, 1995. 
You can book a tour for 100 pesos and will last for 1 hour.</content></blog><blog><title>Boac Cathedral </title>
<author>Roniel Lora</author><date>2023-05-27</date><content>The church was constructed facing east with its 
rear overlooking the lower town, called labak by the natives, in 1756. It was seen to serve as a refuge of the 
townspeople against pirate attacks prevalent in the era, in addition to its purpose as a place for worship when 
it was finally built in 1792.</content></blog><blog><title>Casa Real</title><author>Raj Kumar Paul</author><date>2023
-05-27</date><content>The Casa Real was a two-storey building made of the best available local materials from 
hardwood as floorings and walls to sillar, adobe stones, as walls particularly on the ground floor level. It was 
entirely roofed with tisa, roof tiles, produced at the 'magapog' plant that the Jesuits set up in Mogpog 
originally for the construction of the Boac Church.

The new Casa Real building that now stands at the original site officially adopted as a park, “Liwasan ng Kalayaan”,
was constructed seven years ago by the municipal administration of Mayor Roberto J. Madla, its design inspired by 
the original building.</content></blog><blog><title>Laylay port</title><author>Raj Kumar Paul</author><date>2023-
05-27</date><content>Strategically located landing port during the Spanish, American and Japanese periods of 
colonization/occupation. The site is where American troops first landed ashore on April 25, 1900.  Gov-Gen. 
Leonard Wood landed here on December 10, 1922, Gov-Gen. Theodore Roosevelt, Jr. on April 10, 1932, as well as 
other personages during its commercial operation.</content></blog><blog><title>Boracay(Capala)</title><author>
Roniel Lora</author><date>2023-05-27</date><content>Globaly known as "The Home of the mystic arts" where doctor 
stranger rigurously trained under the supervision of Raj Kumar Paul the head of kamar-taj.</content></blog></blogs>
